Pouya Aghahoseini

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT · AMIRKABIR UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

No.16, Tavakol Alley, 17-Shahrivar Ave, Tehran, 1153963716, Iran

🛮 (+98) 9102117201 | 🚾 pouyaaghahoseini@gmail.com | 🌴 pouyaaghahoseini.github.io | 🖸 pouyaaghahoseini | 🛅 pouyaaghahoseini

Summary_

Currently studying Computer Science at Amirkabir University of Technology. Adept to code in C/C++, Python, and MySQL and also familiar with numPy and Pandas Libraries. During my recent years in Amirkabir, I have had the opportunity to gain lots of teamwork experiences, through course projects and more significantly, through extracurricular activities in student scientific chapter.

Skills

Programming C/C++, Python, R, MATLAB

Web Technologies HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL

Libraries numPy, Pandas

Operating Systems Linux, Windows

Miscellaneous MFX, Jupyter, Git, Microsoft Office, GAMS(Optimization), Database Design

Education

Amirkabir University of Technology

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Tehran, Iran

2016 - Present

Major in Computer Science, CGPA: 17.28/20

Allameh Helli High School

DIPLOMA IN MATHEMATICS AND PHYSICS

Tehran, Iran

2012 - 2016

• Grade: 18.5/20

Experience _____

TEACHING ASSISTANT

Math & Computer Science Faculty, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

Sep 2018 - Present

- Design and Analysis of Algorithms
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- · Fundamentals of Programming: C Language
- Compilers
- Introduction to the Theory of Computation

Student Scientific Chapter, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

Mar. 2018 - Mar. 2019

- Organized Data Science Seminars And Workshops.
- Coordinated 5 ACM Contests.

HEAD OF INFORMATICS AND COMPETITIONS

- Arranged On-Site Visits To Leading Tech Companies In Tehran.
- Arranged Talks With Alumni Currently Studying Or Working Abroad.
- Held 2018 New Student Orientation Program.
- Organized And Instructed Exam Preparation Classes(Calculus, Programming, Differential Equations).

11th Winter School on Computational Geometry, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

Organizing Committee Member

March 2019

- The Winter School on Computational Geometry is held every year by Math and Computer Science Faculty, in collaboration with IPM Institute for Research in Fundamental Sciences.
- Notable researchers in computational geometry are invited for seminars and workshops in this program.